Hello.
こんにちは
It's beautiful.
き れいですね
Well, I'd like to ask you something right away.
じゃあ早速聞いていきたいんですけど
How old are you now?
今、何歳なんでしょうね?
I'm now 18.
今、18になりました
How old do you have to be to work?
お仕事は何歳というんですか?
It has changed to the study of menstrual students.
生理生の学に変わってます
That's what it is.
そういうことね
I think this is my first time doing this shoot.
この撮影は初めてだと思うんですけど、
What does it feel like?
どんな感じでしょうか?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Is it fun?
楽しいですか?
I heard earlier that it was different, but surprisingly, he doesn't dislike it.
さっき違ったと聞きましたけど、 意外に嫌いではないという
I don't hate it.
嫌いではないです
It's really cute.
すごい可愛いんですね
I saw a little bit of Jisan Tokimeki.
ちょっとじさんときめき見ましたね
Who am I supposed to do to such a young girl?
こんな若い子に、 私に誰のことしちゃっていいのかしら
Next, may I ask your height?
じゃあ続いて、身長を聞いていいですか?
It's about 150.
150くらいです
Is your weight okay?
体重はいいですか?
What is your favorite body?
好きな体は?
Number 111.
111番
It would be embarrassing if you were photographed.
撮られたら恥ずかしいよね
I'm not used to it.
慣 れてない
Can I stand for a moment?
ちょっと立っていいですか?
Fisting is also slow.
フィストも遅いし
Ah, this.
あー、これね
It's the Alfal one.
アルファルのやつだ
Okay, this is it.
いいですね、これこれで
So, how about you stand there?
じゃあそこで、立ってみる?
Such a cute high school girl, for sure.
こんな可愛い女子高生、確かに
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうだ
Is it okay to ask about the number of experienced people?
経験人数ってこれ聞いていいのかな?
I haven't done that much.
あんまりしたことがないね
It's disgusting though.
気持ち悪いですけど
But it's okay.
でも良いです
noisy?
うるさい?
Those are cute panties.
可愛いパンティですね
Which clothes are you wearing above?
上の服、どっち?
It's not cold.
寒くないです
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Please tell me it's cold.
寒くて言ってくださいね
It's amazing how big your breasts are.
すごい おっぱい気ですね
A little more.
もう少し
Even though she's short, her boobs are strong.
身長が低いのに、おっぱいも強くて
That's terrible.
やばいですね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's amazing.
すごいですね
sorry
ごめん
You know, I stood there for a long time.
ね、 ずっと立たしちゃって
Shall we sit down?
座ろうか
That's amazing.
すごいですね
It's beautiful.
美しいですね
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
few
少
It's disgusting.
し 気持ち悪いですね
I've taken both.
どっちも取っちゃってる
It's a huge wound here.
すごい傷ですね、ここ
I've taken care of both of these.
こっちの両方、手入れちゃってさ
Hold it yourself.
自分で抱えて
wonderful.
素晴らしい
It's a bear insect.
くま虫ですよ
That's good, isn't it?
良いですよね
Can I head towards Earth?
地球に向かっていいですか?
Stretch your face
顔を伸びて
Can you go?
い ける?
Can you grow your face?
顔を伸びていける?
That's amazing.
すごいよね
Down.
下
Both of these.
こっちの両方
superior.
上
one
一
Yes, above.
応、 上
Sit down.
座って
Oh yeah, let it out.
そうそう、出して
It's okay among them.
中でも大丈夫
Can I take it out?
出していい?
terrible.
やばい
Show your face.
顔を出す